Hi everyone in this video I'm going to show you how to navigate the site. So
this
is the new version of the site. This is the home page so as you can see this is
showing you people who are on cam showing you some movies and galleries and
whatnot. Along the top here are a few different options you can go to. You can
click on direct cam and then here on online now it shows you everyone online
so this is where you can check to see yourself online when you log on. Same for
phone charts and SMS charts as well. So this mail icon here is for the emails
so
you just click into there and then it will take you to your emails with your
clients. We recommend viewing and replying to your emails as much as you
can as you'll get a lot of clients in there asking you special requests, asking
you on your online and it's just a really good way to clean up regular clients
in
between calls. I won't click into mine now just to give my clients some
privacy and not to share their information on this video but if you
click right in there it takes you directly to your emails. Okay so here on
the right side this is where you're going to click to be able to edit your
profile look at your credits and everything else. So here on credit balance.
Now the
balance that you see here isn't necessarily your exact balance that's
what you just have at the moment but maybe you've already been paid on some
of this. So for more information on how to work out your credits please go to
our
credit video but you'll click into credit balance and then you have the
option to view your statement. So in here this is where you want to take a
proper look at your credit statement. Okay let me go back. Okay and now here we
can take a little look at the profile. So if we click on my profile then we
have
all of the different options of what we want to do here so we can edit the
profile. We can view the profile, we can look at the location details so yeah
it's
all pretty self-explanatory but the main one you're going to be looking at is
the edit profile section. So you just click on there and then that's where you
're
going to edit everything, your photos, your bio, videos and everything else.
Okay so we'll click back on this tab here and yeah this is just as you can see
all the different options as to where you can go through the site. Click here
on
my direct cam and then this is where you're going to be able to set your
availability and bid for the front page. So of course here you can click on
availability and then you can start to set that here so you can set your
available hours. You can do your positioning, you can set special offers
and you can edit your direct cam settings. So down here click on direct
cam settings and then you're going to want to make sure you have your group
chat and private chat enabled and that you have your rate set in each one. You
can always change your rate so if it's a little bit quieter you can lower your
rate and if it's really busy you can hire your rate and then this section here
is
where you're going to enable or disable free preview. So when you're doing free
preview you can just tick this box. This one here will allow guests so people
who
actually aren't registered on the site to view you for free. I wouldn't click
this
one to be honest because it's better to just have people who already registered
on the site so we're not going to click that one but you can click this one
here
enable free preview and then you can set for how long you want them in your
room
for so you can have them in for five minutes and then after five minutes they
get kicked out but then they can retain within an hour. So it's entirely up to
you
how you set it. This is how I have mine but you can put it for ten minutes, two
or fifteen, twenty whatever you want and then you can say you know they can
stay
in their unlimited time or you know they can only stay in for five minutes
every three hours for example whatever it is it's entirely up to you. I wouldn
't
recommend having them in there for an unlimited amount of time because you
don't want that. You don't want them in there for free all the time you want
them
to see for a few minutes and then take you to a paid chat. So if I was to want
my
free chat on now I would just go down and press save and that will save that
and then again when you want to tick it off just don't tick it and press save.
Finally this section at the top here is where you enable and disable direct
IM so that is direct chat so it's basically just like webcam but without
the webcam so you're just typing away. So now direct IM is enabled and that
will
take off your webcam services so that basically means that you are only going
to be available for direct IM now so because of that you're going to want to
lower your rates so this is going to be the rate for direct IM now that that's
ticked and when it's unticked it goes back to the rate for webcam. So while
that's
ticked while you're on direct IM we need to lower the rate a little bit as the
rates are just lower on there and they don't pay as much for direct IM as they
would webcam so maybe you can put in 1.10 and 1.7 for example so that would be
my new rate for the moment and then I'll just click save and then that would
put
me on direct IM. I'm just going to untick that because I'm not using that now.
Okay so now let's go live on webcam so we're just going to click here and start
direct cam always want to click allow and you should come up on the screen
there we go okay so make sure there are no animals no photos and no people in
your cam you are the only person who's allowed in here and you can either have
your microphone on or off so now it's on because it's green if we click this
that's the microphone off so no one can hear you and as you can see up here on
the top right we click start you just got to confirm that you're the only
person to be shown in the broadcast and as you can see here you have your group
mode and your private mode enabled confirm and now we'll start to load and
log you on so as you can see this orange boost button here basically the
boost button boost you to the front page per hour so we are now coming up to
the
next hour so within the next five or so minutes I will actually start to get
up from to the screen asking me if I want to boost which is actually quite
helpful that remind you and if you see that way so this is good but you can
just click here on boost and then this will pop up what I always do is I always
mine itself the credits just to see okay so free credits is orange medium we
don't
want medium we always want it to be green so we need to put in at least four
credits to be on the front page for the next hour now what I normally do is I
normally put in an extra credit then it asks for because then it's definitely
going to guarantee me to be at the front and maybe even at the very top so I
would
do that and I would click big to boost I'm not gonna do that now but that's how
you do it so you have to do that every hour that you want to be on the front
page I personally recommend doing it as much as possible as long as you're
making the money back of course and you're doing well because if you're on the
front page you're a lot more visible and yeah so that's me now I'm online I'm
waiting for calls right now and up here next to the boost button on the top
right
you click on settings you can actually even modify your price per minute turn
on your free preview you know take a look at what devices you're using what
camera or microphone you can actually do a lot of it in here as well so you don
't
have to go back onto the edit profile section if it all be done from here but
I will show you you do need to log out and or stop broadcasting I should say
before changing any of this so let's say for example I want to put on my free
mode as you can see it's locked me off because you have to lower before doing
that and now it will automatically start again and I will be on free mode and
as
you can see it and put your mic back on so remember every time you'll mic back
off if you do want to ask or if you want to use your audio you can go ahead and
keep it on so yeah that's all for now I hope this was helpful and always let us
know if you need any more help or advice that we haven't covered in these
videos but yeah hope everyone has a lovely day and we'll chat soon